<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://zhangquanwei962.github.io</id>
    <title>DIARY MYSELF</title>
    <updated>2020-05-20T03:01:59.500Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://zhangquanwei962.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>YOU AND ME ARE BEST FOR EVERYONE !</subtitle>
    <logo>https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, DIARY MYSELF</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farewell (Increasingly Be Lowliness)]]></title>
        <id>https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/post/the-more-i-make-the-less-i-resist/</id>
        <link href="https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/post/the-more-i-make-the-less-i-resist/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-05-17T12:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h5 id="only-love-i-love-regradness-of-what-she-is-love-of-i-love-thats-enough">Only love I love, regradness of what, she is love of I love. That's enough!</h5>
<h1 id="one-of-the-life-wrong-attitude-you-love-me-so-reality-and-despair">One of the life wrong attitude --- you love me, so reality and despair.</h1>
<p>If somewhere is discomfort for you, please just neglect it, thanks!</p>
<p>First, I dare to tell u, on the 13:14, Mar 25, I use the platom to give you a text, the content is short. Maybe you had guessed who sent you, so bad for me due to my weakness that being afraid to the chance of whether you would accpet or refuse. I really remember that you call me at the New Year's Day, pearsonally, a little shocked I am, I didn't know why you pull a visual telephone at around 11:23. Hum,..... I believe it's fortunate when it comes to that situation, after all I was in the front of the library -- bell tower cerebrating the new year. There's many people where we got together and saw the play so that my phone network was broken competletly though I didn't realize how time you had waitted for it. But I received it accidently and with the shock I answered it, later, I see you the first time and the last time I had. U said to me the happy new year, and I'm still not forgotten what you first said &quot; You had scared me, zhangquanwei.&quot; Possibly, you never thougth me would stayed a so noise place, no guard against. HaHa, a little for me, I also didn't think someone would call me on that time.</p>
<p>Then what a pity for only three minutes' communication of bad network. After that, at the corner of 12:00, with the bell ringing, I left there and called you against, but your roommates had already slept, no accpeting, and we chatted half an hour with pleasure. Don't know your feeling, should be the same as me. HaHa, when I got doc, I found Qiu Saitao going through his lovelorn, meanwhile, he decided to play LOL in the Internet bar, as his good fridend, with the impulsion, I went, too.</p>
<p>But rethinking this issue, I regret it XiXi, because of how cold and no air conditioner or heating, I felt my fingers couldn't control, swell entirely. Importantly, I didn't how to play LOL, which made me crazy, sleepy and tired. Besides, in the morning, I came back the school, text you the txt, you replyed me a few words, crediting me 🤣. As for me, just flying when I walked on the road, on the contrary, I entered the classroom excatly the study room, sleeping about two hours to review my courses and pass the exam.</p>
<p>Next we didn't have much exchange, always considering you are a little hard to close. On the hand, according to the understanding of you, you are merely not outgoing with men. On the other hand, I'm not sure what I feel, using a popular sentence -- <strong>I am thinking the peach!</strong></p>
<h2 id="ago-at-the-school">Ago At The School</h2>
<p>At the senior high school, I mean, I could be a little smart but I don't believe it is true, by studying hard and realizing we had learned, everyone could achieve that top in our school. Depending on the two years' knowledge, I could rise to the occasition easily. In other words, showing off is enough, escaplly for you hh, so we became from the strangers to friends quickly. What's more, I found you are poor to physics and math, just right I studyed well, so many chances we could possess. That is wonderful to teach you the question and watch your confusion and understanding expression, isn't it? I also remembered I always ask you to hear me or help you solving the problem. How wonderful and happy I felt that never forget your politeness and shy facial emtion,<s>as we said, love the person you love, how simple, instead of needing more.</s>.<strong>Actually</strong>, <strong>I just take for granted, in other words, thinking peach.</strong><br>
**</p>
<h2 id="current-freshman">Current, freshman</h2>
<p>Just as the first I told, we didn't go through much. just remember in the last a few days I did't send message, you initiative to ask me &quot;Yo, does there review busily? &quot; and so on. That made me happiness that you initiative to talk with me, simply it is. After a short conversation, I learnt about that you had gone the winter vacation finishing all tests, waitting for the outcome. How fast your school make, when I release, only twenty eight left... At the last time, I just ate instant noodles everyday of a box I bought of my lazy across the sixth floor getting canteen, hh. Never beg so much, just wonder to go along with you and know what had happened.</p>
<h2 id="current-sophomore">Current, sophomore</h2>
<p>You know, I have a ex at the first term, yes, I have and commit the truth. At the Tomb-sweeping Day, you told me you planed to travel in LuoYang, how excited I am. I should have stayed at the doc, for seeing you, I intended to go there. Then I asked you the hotel where you live, and immediately, search it to find out whether it is avalible. Yeah, it had a few empty rooms, but the big bed room, with the high price. I preseved it without enough reflect, about six hundred RMB, after I spent it, only 300 left that month. However, I believed I couldn't afford it so apply the refund, where it said that once you finish payment, it can't be refund. Luckily, it's the festival that they don't worry about the guests, almost every hotel being filled full. And you rejected I seek you letting me alone to travel avoiding the awkward, because we aren't sweetheart lover or somehow. I left there at night taking the high subway, only two days.</p>
<p>After that, I ever tried my best to chat with you, and your attitude I felt so normal with a little lazy, <s>sometimes I sent tens you only replyed ones(exaggerate)</s><br>
I am so timid(afraid) to speak u, until now, so I choose a text but not many, many only lets you guess I am. So the day is peaceful and no accident occured, we began the new life without each other.</p>
<p>Several days, I met a girl I ex, she is not the style i like, just coming out the occasion. She's outgoing and good at expressing, without any doubt, I quickly got her but only one meet after we know about ten days , because we met on the Internet. To be honest, I regret it when we make relationship, I found I did't love or like her at all, maybe a little Zha, either no said any words like &quot; I love you &quot;. It's a accident that it is with not longer time. So I began away from her and said byebye several days. Not know how to face you, your imessage I also remember -- a carbon of &quot; 恭喜恭喜🎉&quot; as a ghost, I afraid and really have no idea. Maybe it would last the whole university. <s>Sorry for that sincerely.</s></p>
<p>Accidently, you asked me what I do these days in the last of the term, I 'm preparing the test and always stayed up late until one or two or three o'colck at the midnight. You guess I must review with my girl friend, actually, not, with a little astonishment, using the Ant Pay. Every time you send the imessage, I will reply quickly, afraid of losing the chance I possess once again. On those days, receiving you message is the happiest I feel, on the vacation, we sometimes chat on WeChat but last little you or I did't care, I guess you, so I lose on my way again.</p>
<p>So far about twelve days, I had sent you a video about Ma Ke Si, the topic of us begining to open, very enjoyable with you. Mostly, you as a listener, I as a tell, on WeChat we maybe treasure every seconds we talk (Maybe I am thinking the peach again). What's more, I found I fall in love with you deeply <s>Not thinking the peach?</s>. <s>Loving is not because of the appearance but the feeling I appreciate, which doesn't mean you're not beautiful.</s> <s>In my dream, I miss you and realize you have sent message that causes me weak up one more time, which as the Wang Yiyun's comments say -- Do you know what it's like to miss the best. I once sent him a good night, wake up seven times a night to read the mobile phone information. It was that terrible and hazy consciousness. In the dream, he seemed to return my message, and then consciousness took me out of the dream and immediately went to look at my mobile phone. You see, it's probably that the yearning goes deep into the marrow, and even the dream won't let it go. I can't be free until I tell you the truth either your choice.<strong>(@WanyYiYun's comment)</strong></s></p>
<h1 id="finally">Finally</h1>
<p>Actually, I can't confirm whether you love me, in my deep mind, I am a enormous short coming and afraid that I tell you make unhappy so that losing anything we ever own, which cannot be ruled out thinking peach. After all, I am not handsome and tall enough, you have said <strong>almost every girl is Hua Chi</strong>, but I know you aren't.</p>
<p>Actually, I have gone to playground or watched a movie with the other girls, like the TaiWan twins or more beautiful but no feeling about that. The same as to them must be, after all, we're all not right for each other.<br>
All the days I can't persuade myslef lasting to treasure up. As we grow up, I believe I had better make choices for myslef regardless of how result it is, at least I ever go through, even being refused. The feeling you give is the same as I want, no reason.</p>
<p>It's widely known that we will choose the right from the four answers when we do multiple choice questions, meaning if we know and surely enough, you can get the score. For another thing, there's 25% chance we can make right, however, I have 50% in this bet, although I always choose the wrong, I still would like to try it for no regret!</p>
<p>I still conserve the photo we seldomly have, your simile is so sweet and impress me, <s>Here is <a href="http://b290.photo.store.qq.com/psb?/V11dHpXd2iN2GT/aILz2HEoOs4I.fVsZDweVBV.ajW99z9ns10*5P5D3kI!/b/dCIBAAAAAAAA&amp;ek=1&amp;kp=1&amp;pt=0&amp;bo=OASgBQAAAAARF7k!&amp;tl=1&amp;vuin=2875569757&amp;tm=1589760000#sce=14-1-1&amp;rf=v1_iph_sq_6.5.0_0_hdbm_t-4-2">the photo</a></s></p>
<p><s>I would like to stay up late with you, accompany you watch the variety of shows, cook simpleness to fill self, study and encourage and bring happiness to you and so on. <s>Why not we never try it?</s> Do u agree?  ***Wang Yanfang.***</s></p>
<p><strong>As we graduate from senior high school, which signs we don't have much common or intersection each other. It is me that cause you ~~spend ~~ waste a lot of time where is no meaning for you, so pity for that, recently I have realized it you live your life in your style not me.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Maybe when you see this page, the decision what I make has been reverted or some else. Regradness of how it will be, thanking to your patient listening and persisting seeing the message I sent what a little boring, especially brothering you so much in these days. Thanks in advance.</strong></p>
<p>And I mean that just you're my love at this time, not others. Don't beg for the others, too. Because I also know the matter of Wang Ziming, he once always sent message with a girl called Xue Qing, at first, she is polite to reply it. Gradually, she is bored in some way, seldom later, eventually don't reply he. However, he is going on it, finally she deleting his QQ, with the sentence-- <strong>Are you sick or have a hole in your head?</strong> So do we like.</p>
<p>It's my fault that because you need speace for your life, and I just believe u should accompany with me all the time, so selfness that drag you stay up late and so on.<br>
Maybe really loving someone makes he weakness and lowliness.</p>
<h1 id="wish-you-best-and-smile-in-the-future-just-go-ahead">Wish you best and smile in the future, just go ahead.</h1>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Everyone！Indication Myself]]></title>
        <id>https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/post/my feeling /</id>
        <link href="https://zhangquanwei962.github.io/post/my feeling /">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-05-11T13:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="as-for-me">As for me</h1>
<p>Just a very common sophomore student in China！</p>
<h1 id="what-you-would-like-to-dodoing">What you would like to do/doing ?</h1>
<p>Guess it, I will give you the answer later.</p>
<h1 id="what-fuck-you-say">What fuck you say ?</h1>
<p>My friend, don't worry. Take some seconds into account.</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="as-for-me">As for me</h1>
<p>Just a very common sophomore student in China！</p>
<h1 id="what-you-would-like-to-dodoing">What you would like to do/doing ?</h1>
<p>Guess it, I will give you the answer later.</p>
<h1 id="what-fuck-you-say">What fuck you say ?</h1>
<p>My friend, don't worry. Take some seconds into account.</p>
<!-- more -->
<h1 id="whats-your-hobby-of-normal-life-days">What's your hobby of normal life days ?</h1>
<p>Maybe it belongs to Arena of Valor and sometimes I would like feeling myself for some reasons I don't know.</p>
<h1 id="do-you-like-music">Do you like music ?</h1>
<p>Sure, I like listening all kinds of it but only fit my mind, such as <a href="https://y.qq.com/n/yqq/song/001LokF20Yw4xD.html%5D">那女孩对我说</a>, <a href="https://y.qq.com/n/yqq/song/003eWXlz41gcDr.html">Ngẫu Hứng &amp; LOV3 (Be Strong)</a> and <a href="(https://y.qq.com/n/yqq/song/001mgo6u1tLENZ.html)">Way Back Home SHAUN (숀)</a>.</p>
<h1 id="are-you-looking-forword-to-you-will-become-how-and-what">Are you looking forword to you will become how and what ?</h1>
<p>Hh, hum...... Once I imagine it but it's pity that I con't decide what should I do and a little bet for future according to these days.</p>
<h1 id="so-what-you-wonder-to-express">So what you wonder to express ?</h1>
<p>Not now and much, instantly for I make diary in English.</p>
<h1 id="finally-thanking-for-your-support">FINALLY, THANKING FOR YOUR SUPPORT !</h1>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>